Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XXI: Early Exercise Results, 1989-1992
  - Homogeneity Implications, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Jamshidian Conversations, 1990-03-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Cumberton's FAX, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Letters of Faxes on Phone Calls with Ravi V. or Ravi M., 1989-09-20-1990-09-20 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Lower Bound, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Numerical Evaluation of the Boundary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - American Put Mathematica Programs, 1990-08-08 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Numerical Results, 1989-09-15 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Probabilistic Development of McKeon, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Probabilistic Development of Myneni, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Perpetual Call Valuation Under GBM, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Perpetual Put Valuation Under GBM, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Perpetual Put in Binomial Model, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Proof of Theorem 1, Undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Put Replicating Strategies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Ted Tregurtha's Work on American Puts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - SpeakEZ (Speakeasy), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Probabilistic Development of Carr, Undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Programs, 1989-10-09 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Pseudo-American Put Valuation, Undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Title Page & Supplemental Material, 1989-12 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - TTD on Carr Jarrow, Undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Upper Bound, Undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Valuing European Put Using a Moving Boundary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Probabilistic Development of Carr, Undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Valuing the Early Exercise Premium, Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Series XXII: Executive Stock Options (ESO), 1984-2003
  - Bibliography on ESO's, Undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - FNMA, 1996-12-31 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Microsoft ESO, Undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - The Wall Street Journal Reports - Executive Pay, 1994-04-13 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Alternative Problem Formulations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Amin, Kaushik; Jump-Diffusion Option Valuation in Discrete-Time, University of Michigan, Working Paper, 1993-03 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - AMOL, Undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Carr & Linetsky, The Valuation of Executive Stock Options in an Intensity-Based Framework, European Finance Review, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Carr & Jarrow / CJM, Undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Concavity of Call Option in T, Undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Dead Ends, Undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - DICALG, Undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - (Indicator Intensity &) Exponential Exercise Boundary, Undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - E^x e^uwt minus lambda gamma t, Undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Ex exp{-lambdaS1(wt>o)dt}, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Executive Stock Options Literature, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - FNMA ESC's, 1997-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Flor, Frimor, & Munk; On the Optimality of Executive Stock Options, 2003-08-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Fractional Integral Tables, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Funding - Financial Research Foundation, 1993-12-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - (Using) GT to Remove Drift, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Greeks, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Harrison - Ch. 1, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Intensity is Call, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Kennedy Equity Derivatives, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - K & S Text, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Trivariate Density of Brownian Motion, 1984; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Laplace's Rule of Succession, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Laplace Transforms, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - (Using) Local Time, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Leads, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Martingale Methods, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Occup. Time as Term in RN Deriv., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Perpetual Executive Stock Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Perpetual Callable Convertible, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Popular Press, 1993-12-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Problem Statement, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - SLSG - Stop Loss Start Gain, 1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Sircar & Xiong, Evaluating Incentive Options, 2003-08-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Specifications of lamda t, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - (Using) Squared Bessel Process, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - TIBS, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - TSE, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Woodruff, Kevin; Hedging ESO's, Management Science Working Paper, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Zero Intensity; Exercise at Exponential Boundary, 1989-1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - (Using) Last Exit time, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Paper with Bob Jarrow, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Accounting for Stock Options, 1992-1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 99)
- Series XXIII: Exogenous Variance Swap Rate, 2002-2004
  - Carr & Sun, A New Approach for Pricey Options under Stochastic Volatility, 2004; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - QD 3/2 Process Properties, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Barrier Options (on both price & lcr QV), 2004-11-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Asian Options under SV, 2004-11-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - QV Dependent Normal Vol., 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Separable Volatility, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Trivariate Problem, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Additive Functionals & 3/2 Process, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Joint CFILT in Quad Drifts 3/2 Process, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - [Killig Killig] via Measure Change, 2004-11-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Links to MR5 Process, 2004-11-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - PDF of QD 3/2 Process, 2004-11-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Carr & Sun, Delta Hedge & Variance Swap, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - DES for Inst. Mean & Variance, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - CF of Xt in Prepared Model, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Calibrating Y to ATM Implied, 2004-11-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Always At-The-Money Non Dimensional Option Price as Stochastic Term Change, 2004-11-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Strike Structures of Stochastic Term, 2004-11-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - PDF of Process, 2004-11-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Heston, S.L.; A Simple New Formula for Options with Stochastic Volatility, Washington University in St. Louis Working Paper, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Implications of SVRH Maturity Independence DH for RN Drift of V, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Variance Swap Rate under Quadratic Drift for V, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Time Dependent PIQ & E, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SV Version of 3/2 Process, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Accumulating Variance Swap in Quadratic Drift 3/2 Process, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Credit Applications, 2004-10-26; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Closed Form Solutions for Realized Variance Derivatives, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Calibration, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Quadratic Numerical Vol for W, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Robust Option Replication, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Wen, Fenghua (Anna); Pricing Options on Realized Variance, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Pricing and Hedging Stochastic Volatility Models, Notes, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Generalized Spectral Expansions & Functions of [Laguerre Polynomials], 2003-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Symmetry Analysis of QD 3/2 Process, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Det'c Term Warp, 2004-11-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Term Warp, 2004-10-2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Time Reversing Generated Stochastic Exponentials, 2004-11-07-2004-11-10 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Carr, Girsanov's Theorem for Semi-Martingales in a Nutshell, 2004-01-29-2004-11-07 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Generalized Stochastic Exponential, 2004-03-10 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Protter, Philip; A Formula for Z + Eh(X), 2004-03-22 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Dividend Stripping, 2001-05-15-2004-11-07 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 3 Assets, 2003-07-05 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Turning One Linear Division Policy into Another, 2002-10-14-2003-07-05 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Ross, Stephen A.; A Neoclassical Look at Behavioral Finance: Closed End Funds, 2002-09 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Ross, Stephen A.; A Simple Approach to the Valuation of Risky Streams, Journal of Business '78, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Stripping [Affirm] Dividends by using Generalized Stochastic Exponentials, 2004-11-08-2004-11-11 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Extensions of Our Methodology, 2004-10-19 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Fourier Transfer of x and Laplace Transform of J in General Model, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Feller Process & 3/2 Process, 2004-10-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Merton Perpetual Warrant, 2004-10-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - g(w)=Ew or dvt=p(t)vtdb + e sqrt(vt^3)dwt, 2004-10-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Prob. Representation of Solution to Elliptic PDE, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Hull White / Romano Touzi, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Futures vs. Formed Variance Swap, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - BVP's for Greeks, 2004-10-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Volga, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Related Papers, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Calibration, 2004-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Other Solvable Models, 2004-10-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Robust Hedging with Variance Swaps / Vix futures, Realized Variance Futures, 2004; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Implications of Term Warp for Robust Replication at Vol. Derivatives under Correlation, 2004-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Series XXIV: Exotic Options Results A-D, 1992-2005
  - (Exotics) Bibliography, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - (Exotics) Book, 1993-08-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Computer Search, 1993-02-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - (Exotics) Conferences, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - (Chase FX) Exotics, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Chase; Mundane Problems, Exotic Solutions, 1992-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, Exotic Products Hedging and Marking-to-Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - CSFP Capital Inc., Credit Suisse Financial Products, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - (Lehman Bros), Exotics, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - LeLand O'Brien Rubinstein Associates, Nonstandard Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - SBCI Product Descriptions, 1992-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - SBC Exotics; Overheads from Glenn Satly / SBC, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Swiss Bank / O'Connor Overheads, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - ABP Hedge, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Accreting National, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - American Options, 1996-06-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Barrier Options (1), 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Barrier Options (2), 1992-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Bermuda Options, 1996-10-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Best of Two Calls, 1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - CB on Best of 3, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Cheeser Option, 1996-10-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Collars, 1999-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Compound Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Contingent Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Convertible Bonds, 1994-1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - CPI Stucture, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Daycount KOKI, 1996-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - DECS, 1993-1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - DIVOC, 1995-1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Digital Options, 1996-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - DIV Protected Convertible, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - DOP, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - ELKS, 1993-02-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Forward Start Exotics, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - End Cdn Call, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - EPO's, 1997-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Pellccioli, Tiers, Lenhart, Gradinaru; Equity Structured Products Weekly Institutional Investors, JP Morgan, 2005-06-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Extendible Call Spread, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Flex Collars, Undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Floating Strike Put Where Strike Has Floor & Ceiling, Undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Forward Stating Option with Cap Determined in Another Currency, 1997-03-06-1997-03-11 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Index Options, Undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Hull & White, Efficient Procedures for Valuing European and American Path-Dependent Options, Journal of Derivatives, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Interest Less Dividends, Undated (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Interest Rate Linked, 1996-07-29-1996-07-30 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Ladder Call, Undated (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Lookback Options, 1993-04-28-1996-06-26 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - KOKI's, 1996-04-02-1997-03-31 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Lock-in Option, Undated (Box 12, Folder 95)
- Series XXV: Exotic Options Results E-Z, 1990-2005
  - LYONs, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Maximum Options, 1995-06-05 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Maximum of n Assets, Undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - The European and American Option on the Maximum or Minimum of 2-Assets with Stochastic Exercise Price, and an Empirical Examination of the 2-D Free Boundary Problem: Implications for Issues of Irreversibility and Uncertainty, Undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Mini Premium Puts, 1994-05-10 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Miscellaneous Results, Undated (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Multiply Exercised Call, Undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Multivariate Options, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Outperformance Options, 1991-09-19-1996-08-02 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Outperformance Basket Option, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Parisian Option, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Partial Barrier Options (1), Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Partial Barrier Options (2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Passport Options Term Sheet, 2004-04-30-2005-01-27 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - PEPS, 1996-03-04-1996-03-29 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - PERCs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Perpetual Proportion Option, 1996-06-04-1996-06-06 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - PERQs, 1996-11-21-1996-12-13 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Portfolio Insurance, 1996-04-19 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Power Options, 1996-02-15-2001-02-07 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Quantos, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - (BT) Quantos Compound Option, 1994-05-11 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - (Currency Protected) Lookback, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - (Currency Protected) Swaps, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Quantos to NMS, 1999-02-08-1999-02-22 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Girsanov's Theorem for Semimartingales & Quantoing, 1999-10-04 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Quantoing in General Setting, 2000-02-21-2000-02-29 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - RNV via Quantoing, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Carr's Canopener, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Reset Options, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Reset KOKI, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Resettable Convertible, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Return on Best Sharpe Ratio, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Return on Best Marhoush Object Function, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Shout Derivatives, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Single Stock Futures, 2001-04-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - SPDA's, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sort-of American Call, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Trax Option, 1996-03-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Triple Play, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Two Factor Exotic Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Underperformance Option, 1996; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Up & Out Call with Rebate, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - VSR, 1996-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Worst of 2 Puts, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Zero Cost Collar Calc, 1996-03 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Series XXVI: Finite Differences Derivations, 1983-2006
  - S.R. Mane; Shift of Interest Rates in a Finite-Difference Scheme, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - General Finite Difference Programs, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Approximation for American Ex Boundary in Finite-Difference Scheme, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Pooley, Vetzal, Forsyth; Convergence Remedies for Non-Smooth Payoffs in Option Pricing, 2003; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Smith, R.; Optimal and Near-Optimal Advection-Diffusion Finite-Difference Schemes III. Black-Scholes Equation, 2000; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Yuste & Acedo, An Explicit Finite Difference Method and a New von Neumann-Type Stability Analysis for Fractional Diffusion Equations, Siam J. Numer. Anal., 2005; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Zhang, J.; Rate of Convergence of Finite Difference Approximations for Degenerate Ordinary Differential Equations, 2006; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Ali's Finite-Difference Model, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Finite-Difference Tricks, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Arb Constr's, 2000-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - BC's for Options, 2000-06-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Nakaki, Tomoeda; A Finite Difference Scheme for Some Nonlinear Diffusion Equations in Absorbing Medium, 2000-11-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Finite Element, 1993-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Finite Elements & First Order CDE in Time, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Finite Elements, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Binomial Programs, 1983; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Cell Aug'g, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Discretizing Potential Term, 2000-08-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - FDB - Finite Difference Binomial, 1987; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Finite Differences & Binomial Method, 1987; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Finite Difference - Put Options, 1983-1984; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Finite Differences, 1994-01-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Finite Differences Class, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Finite Difference - Call Options, 1983; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Forward PDE, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - No Natural BC's, 1999-11-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Functions, 1983; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - d'Halluin, Forsyth & Vetzal; Robust Numerical Methods for Contingent Claims under Jump Diffusion Processes, 2003-12-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Linear Multi-Step Formulas, 1993-1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Lookbacks, 1993-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Operator Solution, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Option Adapted Numerical Schemes, 2000-10-25; 60 Linear Feet (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Probabilistic Interpretation, Undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Quadratic (TSE), Undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Using Quanting IGT to Eliminate Drift in Correction Dominated PDE's, 1999-02-24 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Sateesh Mane, 1998-11-25-2000-08-09 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Separation of Variables, Undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Square Root Behavior, 1994-07-20 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Truncation Error, Undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Unit Source Code, Undated (Box 13, Folder 78)
- Series XXVII: First Passage, 1980-2003
  - Kou & Wang, First Passage Times of a Jump Diffusion Process, 2002-04-16 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Novel Derivations of Barrier Options, 2002-03-19 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Pistorius, Martijn R.; Exit Problems of Lévy Processes with Applications in Finance, 2003-05-20 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Rich, Don, 1993-07-15 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Tuckwell & Wan, First-Passage Time of Markov Processes to Moving Barriers, J. Appl. Prob. 1984, Undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Lateral Chapman Kolmogorov, 2002-06-05-2002-06-07 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - (Univariate) First Passage Times, Undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - FPT of C-U or Bessel, 1993-02-24 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Bivariate First Passage Times, 1980-01-01-1992-03-17 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Kielson, Julian; The First Passage Time Density for Homogeneous Skip-free Walks on the Continuum, Annals of Mathematical Statistics September 1963, Undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Gikhman & Skorokhod, Introduction to the Theory of Random Processes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Durbin, J.; The First-Passage Density of a Continuous Gaussian Process to a General Boundary, Journal of Applied Physics 22 1985, Undated (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Duanmu, Zhenyu; Ch. 3 - First Passage Time Density Approach to Pricing Barrier Options, Cornell Dissertation '93, Undated (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Static Hedging with Time Dependent Drift & Vol (Numerical), 1997-01-03-1997-03-15 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Knockout Swaps, 1998-03-19-1998-03-22 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - European FX Up & Cut Put, Undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Carr, Peter; Static Replication of Path-dependent Derivatives, 1998-04-09 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Carr & Chou, Hedging Complex Barrier Options, 1997-04-01 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Deriving First Passage Time PDF from Options using FX Put Call Equivalence, 1998-07 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Girsanov's Theorem & Siegel's Paradox, 1997-02-1998-02 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - First Passage Time Puzzels, Undated (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Alternative First Passage Time Static Hedge, Undated (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Breaking Barriers, 1996-10-24-1996-11-14 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Double Barrier Option, Undated (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Symmetry, Undated (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Static Hedging of First Passage Time Payer, Undated (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Creating a First Passage Time Payer, 1997-04-25-1997-04-26 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Static Simplicity, Undated (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Static Hedging of Timing Risk, 1997-05-12-1997-05-20 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - First Exit Time & Static Hedging, Undated (Box 13, Folder 108)
- Series XXVIII: Fixed Barrier Forward Valuations, 1998-2005
  - Presentations, 2003-04-2005-10-23 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Integral FPIDE for European Call, 2002-03-02-2005-02-23 (Box 14, Folder 2)